[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":77890,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":97391,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":11493,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":108887,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":15501,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":124390,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":3168,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":127561,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":8533,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":136097,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2877,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":138978,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the secon d one to  it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":8171,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":147151,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":2061,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":149214,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":4619,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":153834,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":4700,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":158536,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":4426,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":162966,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub> 6</sub>  0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":3271,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":166238,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5422,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":171663,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1512,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":173177,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br / ><br />  (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":4876,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":178054,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1478,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":179534,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your res ult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2","1"],"rt":7078,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":186614,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1488,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":188104,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4019,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":192126,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1198,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":193326,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":5567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":198894,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1559,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":200454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":27285,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":227742,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own  inverse  under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":46766,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":274510,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":13550,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":288062,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1642,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":289705,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>?  <br /><b r /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":4848,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":294556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1696,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":296254,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3398,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":299653,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1852,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":301508,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3232,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":304742,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity  under +< sub>6</sub>.","rt":1423,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":306166,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":6475,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":312643,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":23291,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":335936,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can  simply  be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":43564,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":379502,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub> 6</sub>  2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":79475,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":458979,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":7408,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":466390,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":2393,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":468785,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /> <br /> ( Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":19872,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":488660,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":2584,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":491246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /> <br /> ( Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":5599,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":496846,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1470,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":498318,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":9280,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":507599,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":9440,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":517041,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedbac k to mak e sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":52136,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":569179,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":5798,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":574979,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1635,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":576617,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3998,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":580616,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5139,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":585759,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":5034,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":590798,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4551,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":595350,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":7374,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":602728,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":19488,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":622220,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":" What is  4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"4 + 1 = 5 which is less then 9 so it remains 5.","explanation_history":["4 + 1 = 5 which is less then 9 so it remains 5."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":48160,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":670386,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"8+4=12 which is above 9, so 9 is subtracted and 12-9=3.","explanation_history":["8+4=12 which is above 9, so 9 is subtracted and 12-9=3."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":75170,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":745563,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity  under +< sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"0 plus any number is equivalent to that number. ","explanation_history":["When the sum of the problem is equil ","When the sum of the problem is equl ","When the sum of the problem is equal to to","When the sum of the problem is equal to the subtractive of the problem (in this case nine) the answer ","O "," ",")  ",") pl ",") pla ",") pl ",") plu ",") plus  ",") plus a ",") plus an ",") plus any  ",") plus any n ",") plus any nu ",") plus any num ",") plus any numb ",") plus any number  ",") plus any number i ",") plus any number is  "," plus any number is  ","0 plus any number is  ","0 plus any number is e ","0 plus any number is eq ","0 plus any number is equ ","0 plus any number is equi ","0 plus any number is equiv ","0 plus any number is equivi ","0 plus any number is equivil ","0 plus any number  is equiv ila ","0 plus any number is equivilan ","0 plus any number is equivilant  ","0 plus any number is equivilant t ","0 plus any number is equivilant to  ","0 plus any number is equivilant to th ","0 plus any number is equivilant to tha ","0 plus any number is equivilant to that  ","0 plus any number is equivilant to that n ","0 plus any number is equivilant to that nu ","0 plus any number is equivilant to that num ","0 plus any number is equivilant to that numb ","0 plus any number is equivilant to that number ","0 plus any number is equivalent to that number. "],"response_history":["0"],"rt":176749,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":922318,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":14314,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":936634,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":5969,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":942608,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["9"],"rt":3011,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":945622,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"3 + 6 = 9 which is equal to the subtractor in the problem giving the result of 0.","explanation_history":["3 + 6 = 9 which is equal to the subtractor in the problem giving the result of 0/","3 + 6 = 9 which is equal to the subtractor in the problem giving the result of 0."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":86772,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1032395,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Under +9, 2 can produce all the numbers in the system.","explanation_history":["Under +9 ","Under +9, 2 can produce all the numbers in the system."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":78564,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1110966,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a  generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"It is not possible to produce 2 with only threes under +9.","explanation_history":["No, it is not possible to produce 3 with only ","No, it is not possible to produce  with only ","No, it is not possible to produce 2 with only threes in th","No, it is not possible to produce 2 with only threes in t","No, it is not possible to produce 2 with only threes in ","No, it is not possible to produce 2 with only threes in","No, it is not possible to produce 2 with only threes i","No, it is not possible to produce 2 with only threes under +9.","Iis not possible to produce 2 with only threes under +9.","Itis not possible to produce 2 with only threes under +9.","It is not possible to produce 2 with only threes under +9."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":78000,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1188970,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Yes, 5s can produce all the numbers of the system under +9.","explanation_history":["Yes, 5s can produce all the numbers of the system under +9."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":57897,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1246875,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 (i.e. 1 and 2).","explanation_history":["It is not possib le to pr oduce aL","It is not possible to produce aall of the numbers of the system u","It is not possible to produce aall of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9.","It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9.","It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 .","It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 (.","It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 (i..","It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 (i.e..","It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 (i.e. .","It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 (i.e. 1.","It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 (i.e. 1 .","It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 (i.e.  1 a."," It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 (i.e. 1 an.","It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 (i.e. 1 and.","It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 (i.e. 1 and .","It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 (i.e. 1 and 2.","It is not possible to produce all of the numbers of the system with only 6 under +9 (i.e. 1 and 2)."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":77782,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1324664,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value  if neces sary.","rt":22732,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1347398,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 +_n x = 0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 +_n x = 0"],"rt":111078,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1458479,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x +_n y = 0","explain":true,"explanation":"The inverse of a number under +_n is whichever number, when added to x equals n","explanation_history":["The inverse of a number under +_n is whichever ny=umber","The inverse of a number under +_n  is which ever ny=umbe","The inverse of a number under +_n is whichever ny=umb","The inverse of a number under +_n is whichever ny=um","The inverse of a number under +_n is whichever ny=u","The inverse of a number under +_n is whichever ny=","The inverse of a number under +_n is whichever ny","The inverse of a number under +_n is whichever nunber, when added to x equals n","The inverse of a number under +_n is whichever nuber, when added to x equals n","The inverse of a number under +_n is whichever number, when added to x equals n"],"response_history":["x + ","x +_n y = )","x +_n y = 0"],"rt":122047,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1580529,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"If t he numbe r can add up to n+1 it will be a generator.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["IF ","IF","If the number can add up to n+1 it will be a generator."],"rt":80399,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1660934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":13109,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1674044,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":6335,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1680382,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":17657,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1698040,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers  are a mu ltiple of one. ","explanation_history":["In the case of +_6, 4 is not not a genorator as is caanot generate","In the case of +_6, 4 is not not a generator as is cannot generate the number 1","All numbers (with the exception ","All numbers are divisable ","All numbers are divis able ","All numbers are divisable ","All numbers are divisible  ","All numbers are divisible b ","All numbers are divisible by  ","All numbers are divisible by o ","All numbers are divisible by on ","All numbers are divisible by one  ","All numbers are divisible by one a ","All numbers are divisible by one an ","All numbers are divisible by one and  ","All numbers are divisible by one and a ","All numbers are divisible by one and al ","All numbers are divisible by one and all  ","All numbers are divisible by one and all n ","All numbers are divisible by one and all nu ","All numbers are divisible by one and all num ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numb ","All numbers are divisible by one and  all num ber ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers  ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers a ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are  ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a  ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a m ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a mu ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a mul ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a mult ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a multi ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a multip ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a multipl ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a multiple  ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a multiple o ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a multiple of  ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a multiple of o ","All numbers are divisible by one and a ll numbe rs are a multiple of on ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a multiple of one ","All numbers are divisible by one and all numbers are a multiple of one. "],"response_history":["False","True"],"rt":418644,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2116687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":31677,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2148368,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please expl ain in w ords how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Sometimes","explain":true,"explanation":"In The case of x=1 and n=3 2 is a generator, but in the case of x=1 and n=4, 2 is not a generator.","explanation_history":["In The case of x=1 and n = ","In The case of x=1 and n =","In The case of x=1 and n ","In The case of x=1 and n= ","In The case of x=1 and n=3 2 is a generator, but in the case of x+","In The case of x=1 and n=3 2 is a generator, but in the case of x=1 and n =","In The case of x=1 and n=3 2 is a generator, but in the case of x=1 and n ","In The case of x=1 and n=3 2 is a generator, but in the case of x=1 and n=4, 2 is not a generator."],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":210520,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2358889,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is  x +<sub >n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":187439,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2546334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":3421,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2549757,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"32","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["32"],"rt":2616,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2552376,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15 -0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":3507,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2555887,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Triganometry","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Math Analisis","Math Analsis","Math Analasis","Math Analsis","Math Analesis"," Triganom etry"],"rt":36109,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2591999,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":7485,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2599486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recen tly","5  - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4713,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2604200,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":5323,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2609526,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4929,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2614456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3612,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2618071,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":3046,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2621120,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your n ative la nguage(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":8236,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2629358,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":9830,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2639190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Nope.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Nop[e","Nop[","Nope."],"rt":6967,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":2646158,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]